{
    "subject": "resource/Austin_(Amtrak_station)",
    "predicate": "ontology/address",
    "object": "Austin, TX 78703",
    "human_readable": "The address of Austin (Amtrak station) is Austin, TX 78703.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9482423663139343,
            "question": "What is the address of Austin (Amtrak station)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9368589520454407,
            "question": "Is Austin (Amtrak station) located in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9284651279449463,
            "question": "What is the city associated with the Amtrak station at address 78703?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.920228898525238,
            "question": "What information can be found using the address of Austin (Amtrak station)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9088292121887207,
            "question": "Where is Austin (Amtrak station) located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8958357572555542,
            "question": "Can you provide the complete address of Austin (Amtrak station)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8947279453277588,
            "question": "Is 78703 a valid zip code for Austin, Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8901484608650208,
            "question": "In which state is Austin (Amtrak station) situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8067721724510193,
            "question": "What is the zip code for Austin (Amtrak station)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41737058758735657,
            "question": "If you were traveling to Austin by train, where would you arrive?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The address of Austin (Amtrak station) is Austin, TX 78703.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2902_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the zip code for Austin (Amtrak station)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2902_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which state is Austin (Amtrak station) situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2902_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 78703 a valid zip code for Austin, Texas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2902_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2902_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more queries to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Austin Amtrak Station does not have a specific postal address of \"Austin, TX 78703\". Instead, the provided addresses for nearby hotels and properties are correct.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}